so how do you prepare your sermons you
mean this is amazing how do you prepare
your sermons so the way that I prepare
my sermons I also talked about that you
know in my in on my own in my online
course and we'll be talking about that
because it is these are the principles
that I utilized that I utilized when
preparing the sermon I remember this I'm
gonna tell something that's very very I
think I may have told you this before
but uh my first sermon I ever preached
was like two hours long oh my people
stayed stayed and it was two hours long
is because I have put everything that I
ever learned about Adventism into that
one sermon
another member by this time I knew that
I wanted to be a pastor and I remember
being terrified because I was like that
sermon took me like three months to put
together and I put everything in that
sermon that I had known how does a
person put a sermon together every week
like for life right and I was just
terrified I was like if it took me three
months to put together one sermon I
don't have three months between seven
days yeah and I I just was like I need
to start thinking now right you know
about the sermons I'm gonna preach I
started writing down sermon titles well
that's a good sermon title right there
that's why I did this day you still hear
me like yeah that's a good sermon but
this is where those principles really
began to come into play because I had to
learn how to do something which is
probably the last thing I will share
with you in terms of this terms of the
principles here is some is what I call
freestyling mmm many people struggle
with having time to sit down and study
the Bible mm-hmm and I realized that you
know in the hip-hop world you know we
would freestyle and part of freestyling
was you'd have to point you know
pointing to an object and the person
would have to rhyme about that thing on
the spot and make it rhyme with the next
object you pointed to and you have to
make it make sense oh and I realized
that I was doing something like that
when they came
to the scriptures like I would and I
like to say this way I believe Jesus was
a freestyler and here's what I mean by
that I don't think he premeditated
things he was coming up with I think he
was in you know like talking to the to
the crowds and he'd be like consider the
lilies of the field and he just come
with a boom yeah look at the sheep and
the goats right he he would look at
things and then come up with an object
lesson from that thing mm-hmm so I
that's what I found myself doing you
know I would be looking at look at the
grass Wow look at the grass like huh you
know what like when hurricanes come
through the big things get toppled the
houses the trees get uprooted but the
smallest thing the grass it stays in
place try goes before destruction and a
haughty spirit before for the humblest
things are able to withstand the
greatest storms be humble
thank you joy you know so I would look
for object lessons in just the everyday
things of life and that began to teach
me how to be studying the Bible all the
time when you're driving what object
lessons can I pull from driving when
you're washing dishes what object
lessons can I pull from the dishes and
look at this dirty dish ah Jesus trying
to wash me trying to get this dirt off
and some of this dirt is so hard stuck
on it he has to plot the brillo pad the
whom the Lord loveth he chases yeah this
brillo pad is not trying to kill me it's
just trying to get this dirt off right
yeah and ultimately he wants to lift up
that that plate and be able to look at
it and see himself and so now my
dishwashing time becomes gospel time
right object business you learn how to
study the Bible not okay now it's time
for me to sit down you're studying the
Bible all the time you're training
yourself how to see the Bible how to
study all the time
so in in your and this is so rich thank
you and in your online school are the
did the students come to you with their
challenges and they tell you you know
this is this is what I'm dealing with
because it's it's so live it's live
interactive so questions back and forth
hey this is what I struggle with we go
through these principles and and every
week we're using we're doing examples
alright we want to take Genesis 1:26
alright let's do this let's question the
text let's dimensionalize the text let's
and we go through and so people it's a
very hands-on type of experience and you
know I think it's it's helping people to
really get tools that they've never been
able to have access to before yes it's
so important to have the tools is so
important you can't do it without the
tools it's not effectively and nowadays
accessibility is key to and and I love
the fact that you have the online school
and you also have an Instagram where
people can follow you and it's it's at
Ivor Meyers yes okay Ivor Meyers one
word one word at Ivor Meyers IV or are
my ers mm-hmm that's up on the screen so
okay and I'm ver Meyers I'm not that
socially savvy like social media savvy
so with the with the Instagram what do
you do with I know it's pictures but
yeah you know people follow you on
Instagram you kind of let them know what
you're doing what's going on with your
ministry they like to know what's going
on just what's going on you know as you
continue to do what you're doing in the
Lord and that's you know people that
sign up will get access to material that
I'm producing you know different Bible
studies and different things of that
nature so yeah that's great what would
you say are some of the greatest
challenges that you face in bringing
these principles to people I think
people
feeling that they can't do it themselves
and that's my greatest burden is you
know people go to a camp or something in
there like by the way come to an Army
Bible Camp if you want to get the full
experience come to an army Bible Camp if
you can't make to an army Bible Camp go
to my website power the land calm and
you can see the classes there we have
recorded classes we have live classes so
either way just check either one of
those out but I strongly encourage you
to come to Army Bible Camp if you can
just google it online army Bible Camp
and you'll see it but encouraging people
letting them know listen you can do this
yourself mm-hmm you know when people
hear my testimony where they're like
wait you weren't trained you know in the
normal way to understand this stuff when
they hear that I think that's one of the
reasons why my testimony is special for
those kind of people so I'm not saying
you know is something wrong with going
to school anything like that I'm just
saying for those people who are like
yeah I can't get something like that
they need to know that an ex hip-hop
artist found this stuff yeah through the
influence of the Holy Spirit amen yeah